listfree.org 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy | ListFree.org

This policy covers ListFree.org, LTD., RLLLP, a Florida registered limited liability company and any subsidiary of ListFree.org, LTD., RLLLP, (the “Company”) in how the Company treats personal information that the Company collects and receives, including information related to your past use of our services and products available under the domain and sub-domains of [www.ListFree.org](http://www.listfree.org/)™ (the “Site”) and is incorporated herein as part of the Company’s overall Terms and Conditions of Use. 

The Company is the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. The Company collects information from our users at several different areas on our Site. The Company does not sell your information to any third parties.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Company does not own or control, or to people that the Company does not employ or manage.

The Company provides links to third-party sites. Since the Company does not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites.

**YOU ARE IMPORTANT TO US**  
The Company is committed to trying to protect your on-line privacy. We believe that in order to provide you the services you enjoy on the Internet, we need to do our best to protect your personal information. In doing this, the Company believes that it will increase your trust and confidence. The Company wants to give you notices and choices over the use of our Services. The Company wants to create an environment for our clients and customers of trust that will foster these protections for privacy of your personal information. The Company wants to make a rich variety of on-line content choices available to you, either free of charge and/or at a cost that is less expensive than otherwise possible. The Company wants to provide you services and information that you are interested in by offering the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out depending on your interests.

**REGISTRATION**  
When you sign up to use services or products from the Company, you will be asked to register. When you register you will be asked to provide specific personal information such as your name, zip code, e-mail address, date of birth and gender. You will choose your own user name and password. If you use certain areas on the Site you might be asked to provide credit card information and/or checking account information to be used when providing payment to the Company. We also ask you to answer a security question. This is required and necessary in order to issue a new password, in the event you forget or loose your password. We could also use this password to process transactions, help protect you against any sort of credit card and/or checking account fraud and to contact you in the event we may have questions for you. We can and might use this information to contact you about services on the Site for which you may have expressed an interest.

**EDITORIAL SECTION**  
When you register to post an editorial, you will have to create a personal profile. That profile will be made available within our Site to the public. When a reader reads your editorial, they can also review your profile. When you create this profile you can include your real name and/or a pen name, location, occupation, biography, interests, website URL, screen names, avatar, etc. After you register, you will be allowed to submit your editorials and enjoy the other benefits available to you at ListFree.org™.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in a public area of the Company’s website, such as your name, location, etc. that this information can be collected and used by others and you in return may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.

**COMPANY REGISTRATION**  
When you register, you will have the option to create a personal profile, a company profile, a shopper’s profile and/or a store merchant profile. Some or all of these profiles will be made available within our Site to the public. You can include your company’s name, e-mail, website URL, phone, fax numbers, logo, and a summary, including officers. When you register your company you are then allowed to submit press releases and enjoy the other benefits available to you at ListFree.org. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in a public area of the Company’s website, such as your name, location, etc. that this information can be collected and used by others and you in return may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.

**CUSTOMIZE YOUR ACCOUNT(S)**  
When you are a registered user with ListFree.org™ you can customize your account information, once you are signed in. You can edit/update your account information, check your order status, create a store account, add, delete, update orders and store information, post press releases and editorials, write reviews, comments, at any time once you have signed into your account.

**SHOPPING**  
When you make a purchase through “The Shops At ListFree.org™”, the Store owner will be provided with your account information that you have provided to ListFree.org™. You can change the billing, shipping address, credit card information and/or “PayPal” information prior to confirming your orders.

Each Store owner from whom you make a purchase will receive your personal data and order information. Store owner’s may ask for additional information, as you are purchasing directly from the Store owner and not ListFree.org™. Each Store owner is solely responsible for their use of your personal information and any other information they independently acquire from you, or about you. The Company expressly disclaims any responsibility or liability for any damage, loss, or injury arising out of the goods and/or services offered or the content displayed by any Store owner; your purchase(s) of or inability to purchase any Store owner’s products and/or services; and any activities of any Store owner.

If you have questions and/or complaints about products and/or services of any Store owner you purchase products from at The Shops At ListFree.org™, you must contact the Store owner directly and not ListFree.org™.

ListFree.org™ does not give your personal information and/or any information about your shopping preferences or what you bought to any of our partners or advertisers.

“The Shops At ListFree.org™” allow you to submit a review about the products and/or service experience you have had with “The Shops At ListFree.org™” as a registered user with ListFree.org™. This information is made available to any visitor and/or member of ListFree.org™ and by filing out the review form you are consenting and understanding that this information is now the property of ListFree.org™ and can be displayed as such at The Shops At ListFree.org™.

**KIDS AND PARENTS**  
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998 provides safeguards to children who use the Internet by regulating the on-line collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. The Company is concerned about the safety and privacy of all its users, particularly children.

The Site is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 18 is allowed register with the Company, to provide any personal information or to use our public discussion areas, including the Site’s editorial and comment sections.

If you’re worried about your children’s activities or their privacy on the Site, we encourage you to e-mail us at info@ListFree.org or contact our Company’s corporate office at 954-247-8485.

**COMMUNICATION FROM THE SITE**  
We send all new members a welcoming e-mail message to verify password and username. Established members might receive occasional information on products, services, added areas to the Site and/or a newsletter. However, you have the choice to opt-out of receiving these e-mail communications.

Please note: It might be necessary to send out an e-mail to you regarding a service announcement, if our service is temporarily suspended or if the Company is experiencing any difficulties on our Site. These communications are not promotional in any nature and you will not be able to opt-out of receiving these communications unless you deactivate your account all together.

**PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
We store all user information in secure databases protected through a variety of access controls. We have implemented industry standard firewall protection and password to protect all of the Company’s databases that contain your information. This data is accessed only for the purposes specified in the privacy policy. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur; the Company has established safeguards to help prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

**IP ADDRESS**  
Your Internet Protocol (’IP’) address is collected from all users because this information is automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, which could be your Internet Service Provider. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, estimate the number of people using the Site, track your movement within our Site, or for administrative purposes. Your IP address is not linked to personally identifiable information.

**COOKIES/CLEAR GIFS**  
The Company uses ‘cookies’, which are pieces of data sent to your browser from the Site and then stored on your computer. Cookies benefit the user by requiring login only once, thereby saving time while on the Site. Cookies are also used to estimate and report total audience size and traffic, keep track of what pages are viewed and allow you access to certain areas on the Site.

It is up to you to configure your browser to either accept or reject cookies or to notify you when a cookie is sent. The ‘help’ section on your browser can assist you to change your cookie settings. However, you might not have access to some areas of the Site if you choose to reject all cookies. The Company does not use such cookies to collect personally identifiable information.

In addition to the Company using cookies, some of our web pages may contain electronic images (also called ‘clear gifs’) which allow the Site to count users who have viewed or visited that page or to access certain cookies. Any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including banner ads, can act as ‘clear gifs’.

Some of our business affiliates may use cookies and/or clear gifs on our Site in ads or promotions. However, we have no access to or control over these business affiliates’ cookies and/or clear gifs and we urge you to read their privacy policy for information regarding their use of cookies and/or clear gifs.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS**  
Some of our Sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Please consult the other sites’ privacy policies, as the Company has no control over information that is submitted to or on these third parties sites. The Company’s privacy policy does not cover any use of third-party sites, ad servers, etc.

**PROFANITY FILTER**  
The Company has installed a profanity filter, which scans messages before they are posted on the Site. This profanity filter is an effective way to eliminate offensive language from our Site. It is defaulted on and can only be turned off by you the user at your control panel at your personal settings page.

**LEGAL DISCLAIMER**  
The Company takes our users privacy very seriously and makes reasonable efforts to protect your privacy. We will disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties if the Company in good faith believes it has to do so to cooperate in any investigations of fraud or other illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our Terms and Conditions of Use or responding to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from private parties in a civil action.

**YOUR CONSENT AND CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  
Subject to the above provisions, by using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us and the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post those changes so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. We encourage you to periodically review our Terms and Conditions, including our Privacy Policy, for any changes, as once any changes are posted to the Site, you agree to be legally bound and to abide by the changes and other provisions contained in the Privacy Policy and Terms of Condition of Use of which this policy is a part of.

**CONTACT US**  
If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, e-mail us at [info@ListFree.org](mailto:info@ListFree.org) or contact ListFree.org, LTD., RLLLP, PO Box 254, Fort Lauderdale, Florida 33004.

We welcome your feedback.
